Happy New Year 2024! I'm Anno!
Activity, gao! Anno applause again this year!
Let's play Shiritori with Anna this time!
Do you know how to play Shiritori?
Yes, I do.
How about you, Ice?
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
In normal picture-shiritori, you can tell what the person before you said.
But this time, you can't.
You have to guess what the previous person wrote and connect it in your own way.
For example
apple
Ila
trumpet
parsley
Squirrel Watermelon
Crow
Quick.
Wow, wow, wow.
I understand. It's early. Wow, wow, wow. You got it, didn't you?
I'll die if I tell you what the last word is.
I will die.
I'll go first.
Everyone is writing.
Yes, I am.
Look at her.
I've already written.
Cucumber.
You said I shouldn't.
Well, then, let's move on to the next one.
This is the order.
Okay, Junas.
Write the next one.
Yes, yes, yes.
You can talk.
I don't know.
Okay? Yeah! Okay? Okay, change.
Next.
What is it?
It's small.
Small. Small. What is it? A masterpiece? It's tiny!
That one!
Let's think about what you think this is and write it down.
Definitely that one.
What's that?
Four, five.
No, don't say it.
If I tell you, I'll die!
No, no, no, no!
Think of something.
What is that?
Hang in there.
Hang in there!
You think a lot.
I'm thinking like a millionaire.
All right, that's enough.
I know what you're thinking.
It didn't cost me anything.
It's okay.
It's kind of obvious.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I get it.
I know, I know, I know.
Do you want to pass?
So do you want to pass? Pass.
There you go.
That one.
Haruma.
You know what I'm talking about?
What do you use it for?
What?
I know what it is.
That's why.
It starts now.
What's that? What's starting now?
What is that?
It's small.
Small.
Okay, here we go.
It's getting smaller and smaller.
Did you know that before?
I knew what I was getting halfway through.
I got it.
What is it?
Oh, my God.
Oh, no, seriously? I know, I know.
I don't know.
I made a mistake.
You draw well.
Careful.
I'll definitely do this next time.
You're right... your face is that wet.
That's great.
Thank you.
Next one.
No, no, no, next one.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. Do you want to press "yes"?
You want to press "yes"?
Oh!
What the hell is this?
I got it. I got it.
I got it.
That's great.
That was fast.
You can tell by the shape?
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's like... It's in the root.
All right, it's a stick.
No, it's the root.
Don't say that!
Who said that?
Yes, don't say it again.
Last letter.
I don't know.
Are you guys early? Oh, my face is up there.
Next!
You know what I'm saying? Are you okay?
Do you know the one before that? You okay? Do you know the one before that?
I know that one.
You know that one, too, the drawing?
That's the one I drew, right?
I must have somehow driven you crazy.
No, it's not.
Wrong.
It can't be anything but an animal.
It's an animal with two triangular ears.
I'm getting him out.
Do you want a pass?
Are you sure? That's where you lose.
Okay, next.
I bought this.
What the hell is this?
What the fuck is this?
What's this?
What's that?
What the fuck is this?
What? What?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
If you lose this, you'll probably find it.
You'd know if you lost it?
What's that?
It's a spinning wheel.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I guess I'll figure it out.
It's another hard color to see.
Maybe someday I'll be able to just slap it over here.
What's this?
It's hard to see.
I'm scared.
Are we done?
Yeah.
What? Wait, wait, wait.
You.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
What? What?
You don't get it now?
I don't get it.
We don't know either.
I don't know.
Don't you get it?
We're being interrupted.
They're laughing at us.
Ise-kun, give me a hint.
I'll just say "cry".
Not even close.
That's not it.
Ise-kun... No!
He's so confident!
That's not true!
I already know the answer.
If I make a mistake it's the fault of the person in front of me.
I can't tell because you're transparent.
I don't know because it's transparent
I don't know because I'm invisible.
I'm getting to the good part.
Oh, wait.
What? What?
I think I got it.
Oh, that?
I think that's it.
Next.
Oh, wait.
Is it over?
Is everything okay?
If it's what I think it is, it's over.
I'm sure it is.
What?
It's over.
It could be.
Yes, it's possible.
Oh.
It's over.
Finished
Yes, sir.
Next video
Let's go one by one.
I'm Cucumber
You all wrote it.
Next...
apple
Sesame.
Next?
Beans.
Next.
You made a mistake.
What did you write?
You'll see.
Tortoises. I stepped on the wrong bean and the wrong tortoise.
You're right. What did you think it was?
What?
What did you think it was?
Beans.
Beans and turtles.
It feels good, doesn't it? A little bean turtle. Why? Why are you writing turtle? It feels good, doesn't it?
Tortoises with beans. It makes me want to go turtle. Here, sure.
Well, turtles, then?
What's next?
Fried eggs.
Fox.
Cat.
Cat. All right, here. I'll go in next.
Who's next?
Koma.
Mayonnaise.
Mayonnaise is difficult.
I don't know.
How would you write it?
If it's mayonnaise, write it where you can write mayonnaise.
Mike Mike, write it where you can put mayonnaise.
Mike, Mike, Mike.
Mayonnaise... that's very original.
It's amazing that you can express it using only skin color!
It's the same.
It's the same!
They look the same.
If you're going to draw mayonnaise, why not like this?
Skin color is here.
Why is this a lion?
Here's a red one.
This one and this one are so different.
Wrong color.
They match, don't they?
Last but not least...
Pants.
That's it.
Trousers with a dog.
But it was fun, wasn't it?
Did you have fun?
Yes, I did.
That's all for today.
See you later.
Bye bye. Bye-bye.